ああ　見ての通りだ。
That bastard... He...
全部で１５人 集めなきゃいけないんだろ？
Give that bastard an extra punch for me...
現実へ帰りたくても 帰れないでいるプレーヤーを誘う。
Yeah, I got it!
カード分配の心配も いらないってわけさ。
Sorry, master...
つまりは　９人で８勝しなければ ならないってことだな。 相手次第だが　勝算はあるのか？
We're both fools. There's something more important
than the world right now!
まっ　いいだろう　では　行くぞ！ ん？ ん？ はっ！ お！ すっげぇ！
escaped destruction, having been
cushioned by Morel's Smoky Jail, it had been blown slightly to
the left of its original position, barely keeping the building's appearance intact
while maintaining a precarious balance. Nearby, in the middle of the
central tower's lower portion, which had been reduced to rubble
resembling an ancient gladiator arena...
ハハハハ　全力を出せば もっと高く跳べるぞ。 私の垂直跳びベストは １６ｍ８０ｃｍ…。
I am a foolish servant of the King, letting my rage consume me as I hunt my prey.
ん？
That's how I should approach it.
せの！ せの！
That's the impression I should give them.
俺の最高記録を はるかに上回っている… こいつら　この短期間に どれだけ成長したんだ？
Where are you hiding, little rats?
なかなかやるな　まぁ 俺の全力には少し及ばないが…。
Come out here, so I can squash you!
ヤダよ お前　勝つまでやめねえから。 もう１回　もう１回だけ！
I know he'll show himself again...
あっ　あんた　合格でいいや ナイスジャンプ。 すまんな　ガキだから 許してやってくれ。
To exploit the opening just before I explode.
あんた達の力は信用してるよ ただ　今回の勝負は
It's time. Adding inte— Shut up!
誰が　どのスポーツを担当するかが カギになる。 スポーツの種類は 全て把握しているのか？ 俺達が確認したのは この８つ。
While Youpi was allowing a
false rage to consume him, putting on a show of shouting
in order to draw out Knuckle...
勝敗次第では　奴らが さらに得意なスポーツに 変えて来ることも考えられる。 なるほど…。
No matter what happens outside,
my goal is to pin this guy here.
おい　ヤバいぜ！ ん？ どうした？
That's all I need to do!
ゲンスルー組が ９７枚になってる。 えっ！ これで 奴らの残りのカードは… 「一坪の海岸線」と 「奇運アレキサンドライト」！
Approximately one hundred trillion microorganisms, tiny enough to pass between particles of smoke, maintained just enough distance
as to go unnoticed by Morel
この１週間 あらゆるシミュレーションをし 練習を重ねた。 ゲンスルー組のことも考えると 絶対に負けるわけには いかないな。
as, slowly but surely, Pouf carried out
his escape from Smoky Jail.
よし　行こう！
was a large area, with warehouses laid
out in the shape of a dragonfly. Cultural Assets/National Treasures Area B        Weapons/Ammunition Area A
まずは　ボクシング対決だ。
Supreme Leader's Private Shelter Area E
Emergency Rations/Supplies Area D    Supreme Leader's Personal Effects Area C with his warehouse for hiding women.
ハハハ　返り討ちにしてやるぜ。 あいつの得意技は　瞬間移動。
Having learned the warehouse's
location from Marcos, Ikalgo was making his way there by truck
ショートアッパーが瞬間移動で 飛んで来るんだよね。
via a direct, five-kilometer road.
ファイッ！
By the time Ikalgo had reached
間合いを詰めれば 放出系のメリットはなくなる ガードの比重が大きくなり
the crossroads that led to Areas A and B, his Satellite Dragonflies had already
arrived at the warehouse.
拳の瞬間移動をする チャンスは激減！
The door's open...
グッ！
This is a good sign.
いいぞ！ いいぞ！
Palm put Bizeff to sleep
and headed for the palace.
「念」を補助する 神字と呼ばれているもの
When he awoke, Bizeff forgot to lock
the door in his rush to follow her.
つまり　奴の瞬間移動能力は リング上限定
That's the likely explanation.
自ら吐露しているようなものだ 我々の敵では　ない
Brovada's in the border guard area?
勝者　バリー！ やった！
This meant that Ikalgo
勝者　ロドリオット！ フンっ！
had no choice but to face Brovada.
勝者　ケスー！ アハっ！
Brovada doesn't trust me.
よっしゃ！ これで　３勝だ！
Why? Did I make some kind of mistake?
この６人 戦闘レベルは申し分なし 面白くなって来たな お前ら　適当に負けていいぞ。
Stay calm... Stay calm and figure out what he
knows and what he doesn't, in order to stay alive!
あとは　俺がやる。 了解。 待てよ。
What happened during our encounter
that aroused his suspicion? Was there something unnatural
about my imitation of Flutter?
ここからは 俺の好きに　やらせてもらうぜ。 おい　小僧！　表へ出ろ！ 表？　土俵の間違いじゃないの？
I suppose it would be strange for Hagya
to order me to go underground.
遊びは終わりだ 何なら　ここで殺してやろうか？ おい　ボポボ！
But since they didn't stop me on the spot, my mistake must not have been fatal.
そいつは契約違反だな ムショに逆戻りだぜ　ボポボ。 知ったことかよ！
Rather, something aroused an inkling
of doubt in the back of Brovada's mind.
このクソゲームに付き合うのも もうやめだ！ 俺に乗る奴は　いねえのか？
And Brovada's down here because he
wants to confirm those doubts!
全員でかかれば　あんな野郎 ひとひねりだぜ！
Was it small enough that I can explain?
あとは船でも何でも使って 島を脱出できればいいんだ！
Or was it big enough that he
only wants final verification?
うっ！
No room for optimism.
あっ！
I should assume it was a big mistake.
タブー破ったら厳罰 こいつに言ってなかったのか？
Is anyone here? I am a messenger from the secretary! Depending on the response...
いや　ちゃんと…。
No, I have to assume
フン　殺されはしないと 高をくくっていたか　バカが。
that if he has a chance, he'll attack... Or he'll kill me!
よし　次は俺がやろう。
I am a messenger from the secretary!
ちょっと ヤバいじゃねえかよ！
The secretary ordered me to come here!
あんな連中と戦えないよ。
Thinker Bell!
いや　待ってくれ 戦うのは俺達だけだ。
If you're here, you must come with me at once!
説明しただろう？　俺達９人で ８勝できなかった場合 あんた達は戦わず リタイアしてくれればいい。
Messengers were never sent to Bizeff's warehouse.
本当だな？ 絶対に俺達は　やらないぞ！ ああ　大丈夫だ。
This was meant to reassure
Palm that he was an ally.
そして先程の　やりとり
I d-don't know anything about
what's happening outside...
間違いなく奴は　ゲームマスター ちょっといい？
I'm not allowed to talk to anyone
other than the secretary.
そいつ　死んじゃってんだけど 相撲の勝敗は　どうなんの？
She had assumed
ん？　あぁ そっちの勝ちでいいよ。
that this was a test of loyalty by the secretary.
でもさ　こっちは　まだ誰がやるか 完全には決まってなかったぜ？
The other women thought the same thing.
さっきまで「相撲は絶対 俺がやる」って言ってたくせに 誰が不戦勝でも構わないさ。 その後ろの連中の中から 選んでもな。
Each room had a phone exclusively
for communication with Bizeff, so it was illogical for him to send
a messenger, hence their suspicion.
じゃあ　あんた　相撲で不戦勝ね。 え？　あっ　俺？
They believed that a visit from a stranger
これで　こっちの４勝。
must be a test to see if they could
stay calm and follow orders
さて　俺のテーマは ８人ずつで戦う
under unusual circumstances, so they refused to speak to Ikalgo.
ドッジボールだ。
However, that worked in Ikalgo's favor.
おっ。
Is this the place?
こっちは もう決まっているからな。 ちょっと待てよ！ 勝敗は　どう決めるんだ？ １人１勝なんだろ？
Ikalgo didn't have the time to worry about
keeping them alive, much less protecting them.
ああ　１人１勝だ。
There's writing in Nen!
だから　勝負に勝ったほうに ８勝入る　簡単だろ？ そういうことか。 こちらが雑魚相手に 何勝しようと
The characters, formed by aura,
could only be seen when using Gyo.
最終的には奴１人で 帳尻を合わせるシステム
It was less likely that Bizeff
レイザーと１４人の悪魔
would find a message that wasn't
on paper or some other device.
１４人の悪魔とは 奴の念能力のこと！
"Heading to the palace.
俺は嫌だぜ！　８人ってことは あと２人いるんだろ！
If I don't make contact before the mission, assume I am dead."
あんな奴と戦うなんて まっぴらだ！ 俺　もう帰るよ。
Ikalgo had expected this.
勝負が始まったら わざとボールに当たるとかして…。 冗談じゃねえよ！ あんたも見ただろ？
But he still felt as much anguish as
if he had lost part of his own body.
あんなボールに当たったら 死んじまうよ！
Palm...
あぁ　先に言っておくが 使うのは普通のボールだ。 まぁ　「念」を込めれば さっきの念弾と 威力は変わらないがね。 ダメだ　やっぱり帰るよ。 悪いが　命のほうが大事だ。
If Palm is dead or assumed to be dead, use your Satellite Dragonflies and
telepathy to support the team.
ちょっとタンマ！ 今　方法　考えるからさ。 クッ…　マズいぞ 戦力になるのは６人
Got it. Pretend that you're reporting
to your Squadron Leader, when you're actually reporting to Meleoron.
あと２人は　嫌でもクズの中から 選ばねばならぬ
So you want me to feed the enemy lies,
to throw them off?
命懸けなんだから やれる人だけでやろう。
That will only be possible
こっちは６人でも 構わないでしょ？
if they don't know Meleoron is here,
or that I've switched sides.
いや　そうはいかないな ８人対決の時は ちゃんと　その人数で やってくれなきゃ。 １５人の仲間を集めさせた 意味がないだろ？
Which means that, since he
is already suspicious of me, I must eliminate Brovada!
強盗殺人　強姦殺人
Yo, did you finish your mission from Hagya?
確定しているだけで １１件だったかな？
Yeah... I did.
現実だよ　ここは。 え？
Hagya, huh?
ここ　『グリードアイランド』は 現実世界のどこかにある。
Doesn't he get mad when we call him that?
ボポボや　そこの連中は 実際の死刑囚だろう。 奴は　命令違反はおろか 脱走の扇動までやらかした。
Okay, the fake is dead.
ここが　現実…。 そういうこと。
Empty?
気づかなかった…。 疑いすらしなかったわさ。
Whatever, I'll just ask Hagya.
じゃあ　まさか ジンも　この中にいるの？ 『グリードアイランド』の中に。
The suspect is now dead!
ジン？ そうか。 やっぱり　お前がゴンか。 うん。
Once Brovada reports that to the other Ants, I can move around freely.
お前が来たら 「手加減するな」と言われてるぜ。
Still, I never heard anything about
Hagya changing his name!
お前の親父にな。
What's he called now?
やってられねえよ！ 俺は死にたくねえ！
But will they believe that?
帰るぞ！　俺は絶対にやらねえ！ あ…　おい！
I must think of a reason they'll accept
if I encounter any of them.
いいよ　行かせろ。 それじゃ　試合が…。
No, that won't work!
俺が３人分になる。
Brovada opened fire without warning!
そっちもやってることだ 問題ないだろ？
That shows they think anyone who doesn't
know Hagya's new name is an enemy.
ルールを説明する。
Please enter your code number.
内野がゼロになったチームが負け。
The elevator isn't ascending!
コート内の選手は　敵の投げたボールに 当たればアウト　外野に出る。
Don't tell me that he came
down here without knowing
ただし　「バック」と宣言すれば
about the passcode system.
一度だけ 内野に復活することができる。 それと　選手が１人もいない外野に 転がった場合は
This is my chance! I have two options to pick from!
相手側の内野ボールとなるので 注意されたし。
Show yourself!
当たり判定のルールとして クッション制を採用している。
It's nearly been five minutes since
Chapter 7 Bankruptcy activated.
例えば　俺の投げたボールが 敵の選手Ａに当たって跳ね返り
Which means the Nen I've
loaned him is nearing 7,000.
さらに　敵の選手Ｂに当たって 床に落ちた場合 Ａ　Ｂ　２人ともアウト。
Is that enough to guarantee that he won't
pay off the full balance with one hit?
でも　その場合
I just...
Ｂがボールをダイレクトで キャッチすれば　Ａもセーフだろ？
I just have to avoid a direct hit.
その通り しかし　俺の投げたボールが
The worst possible scenario
would be that I'm hit
敵の選手Ａに当たって跳ね返り そのボールが逆に 俺の味方の選手Ｃに当たって 床に落ちた場合
by an attack that wipes out Chapter 7
Bankruptcy, and also deals damage to me.
アウトになるのは　選手Ｃとなる。 その場合 Ｃがボールをキャッチしてたら
If that's gonna happen, I'm better off buying time,
waiting for him to go bust.
Ａのほうがアウトってことで いいんだな？ いかにも。
But that means I'll have to wait
えっと…。 何か質問でも？
for at least ten minutes.
外野の選手が当てても アウトは取れんの？
Shoot... Shoot won't last that long!
もちろん取れる ただし内野に戻れるのは あくまで「バック」を宣言した時の １名のみ。
I have to make him explode once more. Or else we'll run out of time!
審判を務めます Ｎｏ．０です　よろしく。 それでは　試合を開始します。
Before the battle ends, Shoot will die!
レディー…
You look happy, monster!
ゴー！ 先手は　くれてやるよ。
He fell for my trap, for my false rage.
余裕こきやがって。
I've been looking for you, cockroach.
あいさつ代わりに かましてやるぜ！
Make this damn fly that's
following me around shut up! Damn Fly
おぉ　やった！
Every time it squeaks,
I'm reminded of your annoying face!
よし　まず１匹！
Okay, I'm ready to explode at any time.
よっしゃ！ もういっちょ行くぜ！　そらよ！
But I'll be faking it... It's time.
ＯＫ　２匹目！
Adding interest. Just shut up!
何だ　ちょろいぜ。 よし　準備ＯＫ。
Right before I explode, I pause for a moment.
あ？　今　何て言った？
He'll try to attack during that opening.
お前達を倒す準備が整ったって 言ったのさ。 へぇ　おもしれぇ！ やってみろよ！
But if I stay calm when my rage takes over,
I can control my growth. Get this thing off me right now...
か…　片手で止めやがった。 さてと　反撃開始だ。
I'll blow every last one of you
to smithereens, you scum!
受け止める　無事で？
You're gonna die on your knees right here.
否！　死！
The next one...
「ホワイト　ゴレイヌ」！
The next tick of the interest will be the gong.
ハァ…　ハァ…。
It's time.
念獣が粉々に砕かれた これは　すなわち
Adding interest.
このイメージは　一朝一夕で 拭いきれるものではない
This will work. I have time to land one... No, two hits!
ましてや　この試合中に 克服することは不可能 奴は　もうダメだな
I have time to punch him in the face,
and get out of the way before the explosion!
あの場合　アウトは ゴレイヌの念獣でいいんだよな？
Take this, pig!
はい　念能力による交換なので 反則には含みません。
This one's for Shoot!
ただし　ゴレイヌ選手が 内野に戻るためには 「バック」の宣言を必要とします。
And the next one's also for Shoot!
クソが… このまま終われるかよ！
Is something wrong with me?
さぁ　次　行くぞ！
I was never that close to him...
何ちゅう高速パス！
Actually, to be honest, I didn't really like him.
は…　速過ぎる！
I don't even know when he
climbed to the rank of "friend"...
ボールの軌道を 追いきれない！ ツェズゲラ！ 後ろ！
So why am I this desperate to avenge him?
うおっ！
Well, I guess a lot of it is that
we've faced death together...
重い…　まるで ボウリングの球みてぇだ
Anyone who's risked their
life with you is a friend.
ヤッベェな　この威力 とっさに オーラを背中に集中させ
But this bastard insulted Shoot's resolve!
致命的なダメージを回避したか。 おい　手当てしてやれ。
He ignored someone who entered
a fight with him expecting to die?
だ…　大丈夫だ　触るな。
Has he no sympathy as a warrior?
プレー続行不可能となる ケガをした場合
Damn Ant!
その選手は退場となります。 外野としても内野としても カウントされませんのでご注意を。
I'm getting more and more pissed off! I'll give him a third punch for myself!
大丈夫か？ ああ　俺も　なまったもんだな。
Wow... I'm amazing myself!
クソ！　総合的な戦闘能力なら まだまだ俺のほうが上のはず
I don't think my mind has ever thought this fast! And I haven't finished throwing my punch?
しかし　敏しょう性や反射神経 基本能力は　奴らが上
Wait... Is this what they mean? Time's almost frozen.
久しく忘れてたな あの　ひた向きさ
Everything slows down...
もう一度 イチから鍛え直すか
right before you die?
理想は もう奴らにボールを渡さずに アウトを 取り続けることだけど… ヒソカ。 ＯＫ　ボールを。
He stopped the explosion!
あっ　そうか！ 「バンジーガム」なら
He got me!
ぶつけたボールを手元に 引き寄せることができる！
He was actually keeping his cool... I can't stop!
さぁ　楽しませてくれよ このまま終わりじゃないだろうね。
Sorry, Shoot... I screwed up!
フフっ　いいとも。 よし　これで３人倒した！ 「バック」を入れても 敵は　あと５人！
The interest won't be enough to pay for this.
「バンジーガム」なら 何度でも攻撃できる！
It's over...
最後に内野に残ってた奴が ボールに当たった瞬間
Shoot...
「バック」って言って 復活すんのは　あり？
Boss... Everyone...
なしです　一瞬とはいえ 内野がゼロになりますから
Everything is...
その時点で負けです。
up to you.
ああ　分かってる あいつは最後だね。
Thunderbolt!
うまく行けば　「６」「７」　２匹を クッションで同時に倒せる！
Lightning? He's completely paralyzed...
強いな…。
If you're not all big, I can knock you silly!
これで　また　あいつから ボールを取り戻さなきゃダメだね。
I did it! I did it! I did it!
あのボールを止めるには…。 「堅」！ 「堅」！
I'm done! I can't do any more! Crap, I almost died!
ほぉ。 非常に滑らかだ 美しくすらある
I could see the pearly gates... My first task is to get Shoot to a hospital.
修行を積んだな だが レイザーが全力で投げれば
I hit him eight times!
それが　果たして成立するか…
What just happened?
「堅」ができるか ならば　死ぬことはあるまい。
I'm sure he fell for my trap.
ただし 当たりどころが良ければな。
What happened? That's obvious.
行くぞ…　ゴン！
I didn't notice there was an attack
coming from a different direction...
来い！
That I didn't notice a bolt of lightning that massive
ゴン！ 大丈夫？ 全然　平気！ …じゃねえだろ！
I saw him back at the staircase...
「硬」で手と頭を ガードしちゃったから 足の踏ん張りが 全然　効かなかった。
Did he do it?
ゴンの闘志に火がついた
just me blowing off some steam.